[
    {
      "id": "1",
      "category": "category 1",
      "question": "8x4",
      "correct_answer": "32",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "30",
        "40",
        "35"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "category": "category 2",
      "question": "4x1",
      "correct_answer": "4",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "5",
        "9",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "category": "category 3",
      "question": "9x2",
      "correct_answer": "18",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "27",
        "16",
        "19"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "category": "category 4",
      "question": "3x4",
      "correct_answer": "12",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "10",
        "15",
        "14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "category": "category 5",
      "question": "7x9",
      "correct_answer": "63",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "65",
        "66",
        "64"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "category": "category 6",
      "question": "4x7",
      "correct_answer": "28",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "29",
        "25",
        "27"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "category": "category 7",
      "question": "6x4",
      "correct_answer": "24",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "22",
        "26",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "category": "category 8",
      "question": "6x7",
      "correct_answer": "42",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "40",
        "39",
        "37"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "category": "category 9",
      "question": "2x3",
      "correct_answer": "6",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "5",
        "7",
        "9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "category": "category 10",
      "question": "5x2",
      "correct_answer": "10",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "8",
        "11",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "11",
      "category": "category 11",
      "question": "3x5",
      "correct_answer": "15",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "16",
        "17",
        "18"
      ]
    }
  ]